Hey y'all, hey. Welcome back to my
channel. And today, y'all, today I'm
back with another product review, y'all.
And today,
um
y'all know I'm on vacation, but I still
got to keep this content rolling. So, I
decided to do a product review on these
pickles, um
from the QT, um
the QT, um stop here in
Alabama. I'm doing the Oh Snap, um
sweet and spicy pickle. I got that. I'm
doing
the
um QT
hot and spicy pickle. I'm doing it on
this QT hot and spicy.
I'm also doing the dill and garlic, the
QT QT brand. And I'm also doing this Oh
Snap cranberry sweetness. We're going to
do this later. And shout out to Yolanda.
Yolanda, my girl. She told me to try
these out. I've tried the pickles
before, but just the regular ones, um
and this is the sweet and spicy. So, I'm
going to do a review on these,
especially because she told me to try
these. So, I really want to see what
they taste like because I love
cranberries.
So, the Oh Snaps, we're going to do them
last because this is the sweet the
cranberry sweetness, and this is the
sweet and spicy. So, we're going to do
the sweets
last. And so, first we're going to do
the QT QT brands, um the dill and
garlic, and I'm doing the hot and spicy.
So, let's do the dill and garlic first.
So, let's open it. I love pickles,
y'all. So,
we're going to see how they taste. This
is the um dill and garlic.
Mhm.
>> I love pickles.
I don't really care how they are, but I
just want to see how they are.
And with these, they're really good.
Oh, it tastes good.
Impressive, though.
It's cold.
It tastes really good, but
to me, I can use a little bit more
garlic on them. Maybe because it's the
QT the QT brand.
Um
but
it tastes really good, just like a
pickle. I don't really
have that
I don't really taste too much of a dill
dill, you know, dill pickles. Dill is
kind of strong sense of a pickle,
but I definitely don't taste the garlic.
And y'all know I love garlic. I'm the
garlic queen. Like, I love garlic on
everything I'm cooking,
mostly.
But
it's okay.
It's okay for the QT QT brand.
I don't really taste all the dill.
And I don't really taste all the
garlic. It could use more dill and
garlic in there.
Okay?
I'm going to wash this down
away, and then we're going to taste the
other one.
Okay.
All right. So, this one is the hot and
spicy.
Hot and spicy. Let's try the hot and
spicy, y'all.
And I'm just sitting in my car wasting
time, cuz we're supposed to be going to
eat something, but I said, let me do a
park with you.
>> [clears throat]
>> This is the uh what I said? The hot and
spicy. So, let's taste this one. This is
the the QT QT brand.
Mhm.
>> They pickles. They taste good cuz I love
pickles, but
as far as hot and spicy,
I don't get.
For me,
it's like a regular pickle.
I don't really taste all that hot and
spicy.
It's just a little hint of it, but it's
not
and you know it's not like what I I
would I would want it to be like a
little a little power in it. It's not.
It's just a little
hit. Not a Not Not It's like a hit
little hit, but not a kick. You know
what I'm saying? But, yeah.
Uh so,
I feel eating, but
it's not that hot and spicy, no.
Not like I would want it to be hot and
spicy anyway.
So,
I think they were $1.99, so if you just
got that taste for pickles, like
sometimes I get a taste I just want
pickles.
Um
that'll probably work for you. But, like
I said, the deal I mean the hot and
spicy snap it's a little hint, but not a
kick like I would want it in there.
All right, y'all.
All right, let's go to the brand a known
known brand, the Oh Snap. Like this is
the really known brand. But, we're going
to do the cranberry snaps.
Since we're on the pickles, let's go to
this one. This is um the sweet and
spicy.
The sweet and spicy.
And this is like a popular brand right
here. I buy these all the time, just the
regular ones.
Um especially like when I be working and
stuff.
But, yeah. So, let's taste this.
Mhm.
Ooh.
Okay, this is a a known brand.
QT's a bit, but it's just a generic
brand, but but this is the sweet and
spicy and I taste the sweetness when I
first bit into I tasted the sweetness of
the pickle and the spicy I
I taste the spiciness in my throat. So,
yeah.
Mhm.
Ooh.
It's just cold to my tooth, but
I get the [clears throat] sweet and
spiciness. I don't really like sweet
pickles unless I'm use like in tuna or
something like that. But just like a
pickle wise, I don't really want to be
sweet unless it's in a salad or
something like this, but just eating it,
but I taste the sweetness. I taste the
spiciness in this pickle. Uh
Mhm.
I taste all sweet spicy.
It feels like that sweetness and that
spicy kick.
Right here.
Oh, snap.
I taste it.
Woo.
Yeah, for sure, for sure.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Wash y'all that away.
And I'mma finish those.
Those are really good. They they good.
But yeah, I like that little kick and
hit of sweetness, but I don't really
want to just be eating a sweet pickle. I
like it in my salad like I said, but
next right here we doing the cranberry
sweetness
and Yolanda she rated this I think a 10
out of 10. Shout out to
It's Yolanda.
Um so, she was like get these. So, I'm
trying them out, girl. Let's see what
they tasting like.
And this is the cranberries. I love
cranberries especially like in my salads
and stuff.
So, let's see.
Okay.
Mhm.
infused
Cranberries infused with a burst of
fruit flavors. Yeah.
And you can taste that burst of fruit
flavors. They really good.
And as a matter of fact,
if I had a salad right now,
I would sprinkle these on my salad.
For sure, for sure. They're really good.
I like the taste of them. I like the
flavor.
Mhm.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Mhm.
They're really good.
Cranberries infused with a burst of
fruit flavors. I think I already read
that, but
these are really good, y'all. So, let's
rate these and then we going to get on
up out of here.
Okay.
For these cranberries,
I rate them a 10 out of 10. They're
really good.
Mhm.
Oh.
I don't like eating in my car, y'all,
but that I waste some. I got to get I
got to get that up.
But, I rate these a 10 out of 10. If
you're on the on the road traveling like
I am,
get you some cranberries or some old
pickles. If you pass by QT, they
probably have them in other
um
stations, gas stations.
But, mhm.
These are good.
10 out of 10, Y'all know to thanks for
putting me on to the Old Snaps
cranberries. I found some, girl.
Okay.
Um
It's um sassy bites, the Old Snap. This
is the spicy, sweet and spicy.
I rate these a 10 out of 10. They're
really good. They taste like what they
say. The cranberry tastes like what what
it says.
Mhm.
They're good.
They got that sweetness to it.
Mhm.
But, these like I just eat them,
but cut them up in my salad or
something. Yeah.
But, 10 out of 10 for these.
Mhm.
They're really good.
And I just told both of these up.
They're both of the QT deals. I rate
them a I'll give them a six.
Six out of 10.
And that's pushing it because
they're pickles.
But
they don't really uh like this one says
um dill and garlic. I don't really taste
too much dill and too much garlic. Like
they put just it like I said like a hint
but not a kick of it in there. And the
same same with this hot and spicy one.
It's not that hot and that spicy. For me
it's like a hint and not a kick. But I
give them a six out of 10.
And that's what it is. And that's the QT
QT brand.
Um
but yeah, and I think
all of these were $1.99.
Let me see my receipt. I've paid
Well, no. This This Oh Snap! ones was Oh
Snap! um cranberries and
the um hottest uh sweet and spicy one
they were $2.19.
$2.19. I got the water for $1.49. And
the spi- um the QT brands was $1.99. And
all I spent $10.64
on this review.
Okay, y'all. And that's what it is. Uh
>> [clears throat]
>> thanks for joining me. Y'all stay safe.
Be blessed. And I'mma catch you on the
next review. Bye.
>> [music]
>> They don't know me. I like to get it
popping in [music] the streets.
in my business coming out to choosing
violence. If you see me out in public,
you don't know me.